Guide to the Van Broughton Ramsey Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
- Accession 2019-007
  - Oversized Original Sketches, 1982-2003, undated
    - Courtship: 2 costume sketches on watercolor board (15" x 20"), 1986 (Box 2937, Item 2)
    - 1918: 2 costume sketches on watercolor board (15" x 20"); 1 digital printout, 1983 (Box 2937, Item 3)
    - Iron Chef: Las Vegas: 3 costume sketches on watercolor board (15" x 20"), 2001 (Box 2937, Item 4)
    - Hello Again, 20 costume sketches on watercolor board (15": x 20"), undated (Box 2938, Item 1)
    - Corkscrews: 1 costume sketch on watercolor paper (19" x 23.5"); 6 costume sketches (15" x 20"), 1982 (Box 2939, Item 1)
    - The Troll Palace: 1 costume sketch on Crescent board (15" x 20"), 1985 (Box 2939, Item 2)
    - A Breeze from the Gulf: 1 costume sketch on watercolor paper (15" x 20"), 1982 (Box 2939, Item 3)
    - Habitation of Dragons: 12 costume sketch on watercolor paper (9" x 12"), 1988 (Box 2939, Item 4)
    - Interview with a Vampire: 3 costume sketches on watercolor paper (15" x 20"), 1982 (Box 2939, Item 5)
    - The Would-be Gentleman: 2 costume sketches (8.5" x 12"), undated (Box 2939, Item 6)
    - 1 design on watercolor paper for Opera Gala Benefit,(15" x 20"), 1988 (Box 2939, Item 7)
    - 2 designs on tissue paper for Julie Andrews Tony Awards, (14" x 17"), 1991 (Box 2939, Item 8)
    - 8 color photographs of actors in Sarah Plain and Tall (8" x 10"), undated (Box 2939, Item 9)
    - Theatre Crafts articles about Van Ramsey's costumes, undated (Box 2939, Item 10)
    - 2 poster boards with clippings of men's suits, 1980s (Box 2939, Item 11)
  - Character Plots, undated
    Handdrawn charts of characters for a variety of projects.
    - There Was a Little Boy (16" x 18"), undated (Box 2939, Item 12)
    - The Road to Galveston (14" x 28"), undated (Box 2939, Item 13)
    - The Book of Daniel (25" x 26"), undated (Box 2939, Item 14)
    - A Walk in the Woods (42" x 46"), undated (Box 2939, Item 15)
    - The Feast of All Saints, Part 1 (22" x 27"), undated (Box 2939, Item 16)
    - The Feast of All Saints, Part 2 (16.5" x 25"), undated (Box 2939, Item 17)
    - Ballad of Lucy Whipple (20" x 39"), undated (Box 2939, Item 18)
    - Buffalo Girls (18" x 27"), undated (Box 2939, Item 19)
    - The Oldest Living Confederate Widow (27" x 28"), undated (Box 2939, Item 20)